http://www.igearbox.com/pages/privacy-security

Photo Paper
Solid State Drive (SSD)
Privacy & Security
NewItemExpress.com Privacy StatementNewItemExpress.com understands you concern for the information you provided and used, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. We take our customers privacy seriously and we will only collect and use your personal information as outlined below.In fact, your privacy is important to us. We only use your name and other information, which relates to you in the manner set out in this Privacy Policy. We will only collect information where it is necessary for us to do so. We will only keep your information for as long as we are either required to by law or as is relevant for the purposes for which it was collected.You can visit the Site and browse without having to provide personal details. During your visit to the Site you remain anonymous and at no time can we identify you unless you have an account on the Site and log on with your user name and password.Collection of Personal InformationNewItemExpress.com does not sell, share or trade customer`s personal information collected online with third parties.Personal information collected online will only be disclosed within our corporate group for internal use only.When you create a NewItemExpress.com account, you only need to provide the basic information including• First Name• Last Name• Email AddressWhen you purchase item(s) from us, we may collect additional information such as recipient name, delivery address, phone number as this information is needed for delivery purpose.The personal information we collect from you will be used in some or all of the following ways:• To deliver the products you have purchased from NewItemExpress.com• To update you on the delivery of the product and for customer support purposes• To provide you with relevant product information• To process your orders and to provide you with the services and information offered through our website and which you requestFurthermore, we will use the information you provide to administer your account with us; verify and carry out financial transactions in relation to payments you make online; audit the downloading of data from our website; improve the layout and/or content of the pages of our website and customize them for users; identify visitors on our website; carry out research on our users` demographics; send you information we think you may find useful or which you have requested from us, including information about our products and services, provided you have indicated that you have not objected to being contacted for these purposesWe may pass your name and address on to a third party in order to make delivery of the product to you (for example to our shipping carriers).Your actual order details may be stored with us but for security reasons cannot be retrieved directly by us. However, you may access this information by logging into your account on the Site. Here you can view the details of your orders that have been completed, those which are open and those which are shortly to be dispatched and administer your address details, bank details and any newsletter to which you may have subscribed. You undertake to treat the personal access data confidentially and not make it available to unauthorized third parties. We cannot assume any liability for misuse of passwords.Updating Your Personal InformationYou can update your personal information anytime by accessing your account on NewItemExpress.com website.Security of Your Personal InformationNewItemExpress.com ensures that all information collected will be safely and securely stored. We protect your personal information by:• Restricting access to personal information• Maintaining technology products to prevent unauthorized computer access• Securely destroying your personal information when it`s no longer needed for our record retention purposesDisclosure of Personal InformationWe will not share your information with any other organizations other than related companies and those third parties directly related to the delivery of the products you have purchased from NewItemExpress.com website. In exceptional circumstances NewItemExpress.com may be required to disclose personal information, such as when there are grounds to believe that the disclosure is necessary to prevent a threat to life or health, or for law enforcement purposes. NewItemExpress.com is committed to complying with the Privacy Act and the National Privacy principles.Collection of Computer DataWhen you visit NewItemExpress.com, our company servers will automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. This data may include:• Your computer`s IP address• Browser type• Webpage you were visiting before you came to our site• The pages with in NewItemExpress.com you visit• The time spent on those pages, items and information searched for on our site, access times and dates, and other statistics.This information is collected for analysis and evaluation in order to help us improve our site and the services and products we provide. This data will not be used in association with any other personal information.As part of the above, NewItemExpress.com may use Google Analytics features based on Display Advertising, including but not restricted to the following: Remarketing, Google Display Network Impression Reporting, DoubleClick Campaign Manager integration, and Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting. Using the Google Ads Settings (https://www.google.com/settings/ads), you can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads. NewItemExpress.com also uses Remarketing with Google Analytics to advertise online; third-party vendors, including Google, may show NewItemExpress.com ads on sites across the Internet. NewItemExpress.com and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on visitors` past visits to NewItemExpress.com, as well as report how ad impressions, other uses of ad services, and interactions with these ad impressions and ad services are related to visits to NewItemExpress.com. Changes to the Privacy PolicyNewItemExpress.com reserves the right to modify and change the Privacy Statement at any time. Any changes to this policy will be published on our site.Complaints about breeches of privacyIf you are not satisfied with the way in which we handle your enquiry or complaint, please don`t hesitate to contact us.
choosing a selection results in a full page refresh
Opens in a new window.
Opens external website in a new window.
